Guide to the A. B. Cook Papers 1882-1940
Montana Historical Society Archives
- Mcconnell, Cook And Company / A.b. Cook Missoula Properties
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Minnesota Savings and Investment Company, 1892 (Box-folder 51 / 17)
    - Montana Savings Bank, 1891 (Box-folder 51 / 18)
    - Ellis L. Motte (includes The Realty Company), 1890-1892 (Box-folder 51 / 19)
    - M (correspondents include Maling and Taft, A.G. Mandel, C.H. Martien, A.M. Mason, Matheson and Company, W.H. May, L.F. Menage, Miner Publishing Company, Missoula city and county, Missoula County Abstract Company, Mitchell and Lewis Company wagons, Montana National Bank, Andrew C. Morgan), 1889-1894 (Box-folder 51 / 20-21)
    - Niagara Publishing Company (American Investments), 1891-1892 (Box-folder 51 / 22)
    - N (correspondents include Nathan Brothers, E.P. Noll and Company, Northern Pacific and Montana Railroad Company, Northern Pacific Railroad Company, Northwestern Land Company), 1889-1893 (Box-folder 51 / 23)
    - O (correspondents include W.P. Ogden; Ohio State Journal Company; S.A. Olmstead; Orcutt Company, lithographers; John M. Orr), 1890-1892 (Box-folder 51 / 24)
    - W.A. Pennycook, 1889-1892 (Box-folder 51 / 25)
    - L.G. Phelps (Montana National Bank; Fourth of July Mining Company), 1889-1892 (Box-folder 51 / 26)
    - E.L. Proctor (enclosing proofs of lithography for letterhead), 1890 (Box-folder 51 / 27)
    - W.C. Pyfer, 1889-1892 (Box-folder 51 / 28)
    - P (correspondents include Pacific Insurance Union, Pacific States Advertising Bureau, W.F. Parker, Passmore and Jeffries, George L. Peck, George H. Pew, S.A. Philpott, R.L. Polk and Company, Jules L. Prickett), 1889-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 1-2)
    - Q (correspondents include John A. Quirk, W.J. Quirk), 1890-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 3)
    - Realty Company (B.W. Crowninshield), 1890-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 4)
    - Reeder and Helmick (re Missoula Water Works and Milling Company ditch), 1889-1890 (Box-folder 52 / 5)
    - Fred H. Rice (Western Farm Mortgage Company; Witherbee and Hunter), 1890-1891 (Box-folder 52 / 6-7)
    - Rocky Mountain Bell Telephone Company, 1890-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 8)
    - R (correspondents include W.H. Raymond, J.M. Reed, T.W. Rittenhouse, William L. Robertson, J.M. Robinson, W.H. Roland, D.H. Ross, Kenneth Ross, R. Lewis Rutter), 1889-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 9)
    - R.B. Sherburn, 1890-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 10)
    - M.M. Shiland, 1890-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 11)
    - C.D. Sinclair, 1891-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 12)
    - J.L. Stack and Company, 1890 (Box-folder 52 / 13)
    - Grace Stambaugh, 1890 (Box-folder 52 / 14)
    - A.J. Steele (includes Steele and Company; Steele and Clements), 1889-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 15)
    - S (correspondents include J.U. Sanders, C.A. Scott, S.F. Shannon, J.C. Shaubut, James B. Shaw, W.M. Shaw, A.L. Sherer, E.V. Smalley, Smith and Wyman, E.D. Sniffen, N.G. Snow and Company, G.F. Spaulding, J.H. Suiter, Emma Swain), 1890-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 16-17)
    - T-U (correspondents include John G. Taylor, E.H. Thompson, William Treacy, Underwriters Agency), 1889-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 18)
    - W.D. Vincent, 1891 (Box-folder 52 / 19)
    - V (correspondents include J.G. VanWail, Vermillion Committee), 1889-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 20)
    - Belle Waggener, 1889-1891 (Box-folder 52 / 21)
    - Wallace, Thornburgh and Appleton; Wallace and Thornburgh, 1890-1891 (Box-folder 52 / 22)
    - J.F. Wardner, 1891-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 23)
    - Westchester Fire Insurance Company (James N. Reynolds), 1891-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 24)
    - Western Farm Mortgage Trust Company, 1890-1891 (Box-folder 52 / 25)
    - A.F. Whitcomb, 1890-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 26)
    - J.R. Whitmore, 1889-1891 (Box-folder 52 / 27)
    - W (correspondents include O.E. Wedgewood, F.M. Williams, L.E. Williams, Sara Williams, Witherbee and Wheeler, Wolf and Ryman, J.B. Wood, Frank H. Woody), 1889-1894 (Box-folder 52 / 28)
    - Y-Z (correspondents include W.R. Young; A. Zeese and Company, photo-zinc etchers), 1890-1892 (Box-folder 52 / 29)
    - Telegrams, 1889-1892 (Box-folder 53 / 1-5)
  - General Correspondence
    - B (correspondents include Walter Bickford, Blackfoot Forest Protective Association, Booth and Booth; Booth, McIntosh and Fisher), 1910, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 53 / 6)
    - R.M. Cobban Realty Company, 1906-1907 (Box-folder 53 / 7)
    - C-H (correspondents include H.E. Chaney, J.C. Epperson, E. Firchom, Fisher and Van Valen, W.R. Glasscock, Hall and Patterson, J.M. Hladik), 1907-1909, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 53 / 8)
    - Warren Jones, 1915-1918 (Box-folder 53 / 9)
    - J-L (correspondents include Kline and Keith, Charles J. Lange), 1907-1909 (Box-folder 53 / 10)
    - C.H. McLeod (Missoula Mercantile Company), 1906 (Box-folder 53 / 11)
    - Missoula city and county, 1906-1912, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 53 / 12)
    - M-P (correspondents include F.W. McConnell, S.R. Mercer, Louis F. Nicolet, O.B.S. Orr, Harry H. Parsons, William C. Pyfer), 1906-1910, 1925, 1928 (Box-folder 53 / 13)
    - James M. Rhoades, Real Estate and Insurance, 1906-1913 (Box-folder 53 / 14-17)
    - R (correspondents include A.F. Randall, M. Ratigan, Ross and Violette), 1906, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 53 / 18)
    - Stoddard and Price, Missoula Insurance and Real Estate Agency, 1906-1908 (Box-folder 53 / 19)
    - S-T (correspondents include George Slack, H.M. Small, LaVantia Smith, R. deB. Smith, George L. Steinbrenner, Frank Thomas), 1906-1912, 1927 (Box-folder 53 / 20)
    - C.E. Woodworth, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 53 / 21)
    - W (correspondents include Watson Agency, Western Montana National Bank, E.A. Winstanley), 1908-1909, 1923, 1928 (Box-folder 53 / 22)
  - Financial Records
    - Accounts, 1891-1892 (Box-folder 53 / 23)
    - Bank books, bank statements, cancelled checks, 1889-1893 (Box-folder 53 / 24-25)
    - Bills, receipts, etc., 1891-1892 (Volume Vol. 5)
    - Bills, receipts, etc., 1891-1911 (Box-folder 53 / 26)
    - Bills and notes payable and receivable, 1890-1892 (Box-folder 53 / 27)
    - Financial statements (includes Missoula Syndicate), 1889-1900 (Box-folder 53 / 28)
    - Inventory, 1891 (Box-folder 53 / 29)
    - Loan applications (includes property descriptions, inventories, livestock value, etc.), 1890 (Box-folder 54 / 1)
    - Lot ledger, 1900-1909, 1926 (Box-folder 54 / 2)
    - Lot lists, 1891-1898, n.d. (Box-folder 54 / 3-4)
    - Pocket journal, 1889-1892 (Box-folder 54 / 5)
    - Syndicate sales on deed, contract, and bond, 1889-1891 (Box-folder 54 / 6)
    - Tax assessment lists, 1892-1928 (Box-folder 54 / 7-10)
  - Legal Documents
    - Agreement with The Syndicate, 1889 (Box-folder 55 / 1)
    - Agreement with Peter Larson, 1890 (Box-folder 55 / 2)
    - Certificates of redemption for delinquent taxes, 1891-1929 (Box-folder 55 / 3)
    - Deeds, 1890-1902 (Box-folder 55 / 4)
    - Partnership agreement and dissolution, 1889-1891 (Box-folder 55 / 5)
    - Miscellaneous (includes mortgage agreements, building removal agreements, sales agreement), 1889-1891, 1909 (Box-folder 55 / 6)
    - Missoula properties [oversize maps in OVERSIZE FOLDER 7], 1891, n.d. (Box-folder 55 / 7)
  - Subject Files
    - Proposed Valley National Bank (also includes statements of condition of several banks), 1891 (Box-folder 55 / 8)
  - Miscellany
    - Missoula Power and Irrigation Company flume and ditch drawings, 1891 (Box-folder OvFd / 7)
- Montana Concrete Construction Company
  - Court Papers
    - H.L. Wilson, T.R. Hinds, and A.B. Cook vs. Yegan Brothers and Cothron and Todd (re Park County Free Public High School sidewalks), 1908 (Box-folder 56 / 1)
  - Financial Records
    - Balance sheets for work in Bozeman, Dillon, and Livingston on account Ben Hager, 1905, n.d. (Box-folder 56 / 2)
    - Pocket ledgers, 1905 (Box-folder 56 / 3)
- Montana Independent Telephone Company
  - General Correspondence
    - A-C (correspondents include Charles C. Adams, R.D. Alden, F.W. Buff, H.E. Chaney, George Cox), 1910-1912 (Box-folder 56 / 4)
    - John F. Davies, 1909-1912 (Box-folder 56 / 5)
    - D-K (correspondents include Edward J. Dahms, Exchange National Bank, Interstate Consolidated Telephone Company, C.J. Kelly), 1910-1911 (Box-folder 56 / 6)
    - Thaddeus S. Lane, 1908-1915 (Box-folder 56 / 7-10)
    - M-R (correspondents include John MacGinniss, B.E. Matthews, W.F. McKee, Montana Independent Telephone Company circular letters, John M. Murphy, T.E. Partridge, John A. Roebling's Sons Company), 1914-1915 (Box-folder 56 / 11)
    - Milton Smith (Interstate Telephone Company), 1914-1915 (Box-folder 56 / 12)
    - S-W (correspondents include Silver Bow National Bank; State Telephone and Telegraph Company; Stern, Anderson and Davis; Union Bank and Trust Company; Washington Fire Insurance Company), 1910-1912 (Box-folder 56 / 13)
  - Financial Records
    - Financial statements, 1910-1913 (Box-folder 56 / 14)
    - Ledger, 1909-1912 (Box-folder 56 / 15)
    - Promissory notes, 1910 (Box-folder 56 / 16)
  - Legal Documents
    - Agreements with John A. Roebling's Sons Company, 1910 (Box-folder 56 / 17)
  - Organization
    - Annual reports to stockholders, prospecti, etc., 1909-1911 (Box-folder 56 / 18)
  - Subject Files
    - Billings Mutual Telephone Company, 1910-1913 (Box-folder 56 / 19)
    - Home Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1909-1912 (Box-folder 56 / 20)
  - Clippings
    - Re company, 1912 (Box-folder 56 / 21)
- National Life Insurance Company Of Montana
  - General Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include William A. Matthews, Morgan Edwards and Company, J.M. Dawson, A.T. Morgan), 1910-1912 (Box-folder 56 / 22)
  - Financial Records
    - Financial statement, promissory notes, 1910-1911 (Box-folder 56 / 23)
  - Organization
    - Prospectus, 1911 (Box-folder 56 / 24)
- Shannon And Cook
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - D.P. Sheldon, 1888 (Box-folder 57 / 1)
  - Assay Reports
    - Certificate of assay, 1888 (Box-folder 57 / 2)
  - Financial Records
    - Bills, receipts, etc., 1888-1889 (Box-folder 57 / 3)
- Silver Bow National Bank
  - General Correspondence
    - B-R (correspondents include H.P. Bennett, J.P. Browne, John F. Davies, Tom R. Hinds, Zephin Job, R.X. Lewis, John Maginniss, McBride and McBride, M.L. Rigby), 1907-1918 (Box-folder 57 / 4)
    - Robert T.F. Smith, cashier, 1907-1912 (Box-folder 57 / 5)
    - U-W (correspondents include United States Treasury Dept., Charles W. Warren), 1909 (Box-folder 57 / 6)
  - Financial Records
    - Expense accounts, 1907-1908 (Box-folder 57 / 7)
    - Reports of condition, 1907-1908, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 57 / 8)
  - Legal Documents
    - Agreement between T.R. Hinds, John Maginniss, A.B. Cook, Robert T.F. Smith, and Zephin Job; and State Savings Bank and T.E. Collins for sale of Silver Bow National Bank paper, 1907 (Box-folder 57 / 9)
  - Organization
    - Minutes of meeting, clipping re consolidation of Silver Bow National Bank and Commercial Bank, list of stockholders, 1909, n.d. (Box-folder 57 / 10)
- Toronto Construction Company / Cook, Deeks And Hinds
  - General Correspondence
    - George S. Deeks, 1906-1909, 1915, 1918 (Box-folder 57 / 11)
    - Levi W. Naylor, 1906-1907 (Box-folder 57 / 12)
    - A.M. Stewart (re Deeks vs. Cook, et al.), 1914-1918 (Box-folder 57 / 13)
    - Watson, Smoke and Smith (includes references to Clark vs. Cook), 1906-1907 (Box-folder 57 / 14)
- Trail Creek Coal Company
  - Employment Records
    - Payroll / timesheets, 1899-1900 (Box-folder 57 / 15)
  - Financial Records
    - Bank statements and cancelled checks, 1899-1900 (Box-folder 57 / 16)
  - Organization
    - Articles of incorporation; stock certificates, 1898-1899 (Box-folder 57 / 17)
- Tuttle Land Company
  - General Correspondence
    - Alexander McKenzie, Lee Pettibone, Matteson M. Mounts, 1913-1923 (Box-folder 57 / 18)
  - Financial Records
    - Bank statements, cancelled checks, etc., 1915-1920 (Box-folder 57 / 19)
    - Financial statements, 1916-1923 (Box-folder 57 / 20)
    - List of promissory notes, 1913-1914, n.d. (Box-folder 57 / 21)
  - Organization
    - Minutes of annual meeting; papers re dissolution of company, 1916, 1920 (Box-folder 57 / 22)
- Republican Party
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman Gust. Moser: A-G (correspondents include Ike Abernathy, W.E. Baggs, D.P. Belden, O.C. Cooper, Martin Cramer, E.M. Dinnick, George W. Dougherty, Charles B. Gibbs), 1889 (Box-folder 57 / 23)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman Gust. Moser: H (correspondents include W.R. Hamilton, Zeb. M. Harris, J.W. Hathaway, M.B. Hendricks), 1889 (Box-folder 57 / 24)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman Gust. Moser: J-R (correspondents include Garl T. Jones, R.W. Martin, M.J. McCutcheon, Silas Mitchell, George Miles, James Morris, C.H. Musgrave, T.C. Power, D.H. Ross), 1889 (Box-folder 57 / 25)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman Gust. Moser: A.J. Seligman (Republican State Central Committee), 1889 (Box-folder 57 / 26)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman Gust. Moser: S-W (correspondents include A.C. Sheldon, J.K. Squiers, H.G. Swaney, Henry Therriault, Henry C. Tuttle, Frank Westler, Lyle Worden), 1889 (Box-folder 57 / 27)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County circular letters, 1889 (Box-folder 57 / 28)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman A.B. Cook: A-B (correspondents include James A. Allen, W.E. Baggs, George H. Bell, C.H. Bernard, P.N. Bernard, Alex. C. Botkin, W.J. Brennan, Amos Buck, Charles Buck), 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 1)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman A.B. Cook: C-H (correspondents include T.A. Churchill, R.L. Clinton, O.C. Cooper, Thomas A. Cummings, G.W. Dougherty, J.T. Farris, E.S. French, C.B. Gibbs, C. Gillen, Frank Hatton), 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 2)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman A.B. Cook: M (correspondents include Frank W. McConnell, James A. McGowan, B.J. McIntire, M.A. Meyendorff, J.K. Miller, H.J. Mock, Montana Attorney General, Frank J. Morris, George Mueller, C. H. Musgrave), 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 4)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman A.B. Cook: N-P (correspondents include Robert A. O'Hara, John D. Posten, T.C. Power), 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 5)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman A.B. Cook: N-P (correspondents include Republican State Central Committee members Lee Mantle, Sidney M. Logan), 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 6)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman A.B. Cook: R-V (correspondents include Republican National Committee, A.J. Seligman, J.B. Shaw, Perry Silvey, M.P. Stephens, Martin Toole, A.L. Treat, Henry L. Van Wyck), 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 7)
    - Republican Central Committee, Missoula County chairman A.B. Cook: W (correspondents include C.L. Wayland, Benjamin Webster, John Wessel, M.L. Whaley, W.C. Whipps), 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 8)
    - P.N. Bernard, 1893 (Box-folder 58 / 9)
    - Missoula County Republican Central Committee, Republican National Committee, Republican State Central Committee, 1894-1895 (Box-folder 58 / 10)
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    - Letterpress book: "Campaign of 1892" (Box-folder 58 / 11)
  - General Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Fletcher Maddox, Matteson M. Mounts, John Willis, Frank O. Lowden, Andrew Mellon, J.E. Edwards, Republican National Committee), 1921-1928 (Box-folder 58 / 12-13)
  - Financial Records
    - Miscellaneous (includes bills and accounts), 1889 (Box-folder 58 / 14)
    - Miscellaneous (includes bills, receipts, checks, etc.), 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 15)
  - Miscellany
    - Petition for Tin Cup post office; precinct vote totals, list of precinct chairmen, results of canvas, 1889 (Box-folder 58 / 16)
    - Lists of Missoula County Republicans, 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 17)
    - Schedule of John E. Rickards speeches; appointment of special deputy sheriffs for election day, 1892 (Box-folder 58 / 18)
    - Petitions for Frank O. Lowden for President, 1928? (Box-folder 58 / 19)
    - Campaign brochures for Wellington D. Rankin for Governor and for Republican candidates; campaign songs, 1922, 1926, n.d. (Box-folder 58 / 20)
  - Clippings
    - Political (includes Republican National Committee, Frank O. Lowden campaign for President), 1926-1928 (Box-folder 58 / 21)
- Frank Hervey Cook
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - B-J (correspondents include Engineers Public Service Company, First Seattle Dexter Horton Securities Company, Innovation Ingenuities Inc.), 1924-1949 (Box-folder 59 / 1)
    - LaSalle Extension University. School of Law, 1925 (Box-folder 59 / 2)
    - Frank Hervey Pettingell (includes Estate), 1908, 1925, 1927 (Box-folder 59 / 3)
    - P-Y, unidentified (correspondents include St. Paul's School, Washington Mutual Savings Bank, White Sulphur Springs and Yellowstone Park Railway Company), 1925-1949, n.d. (Box-folder 59 / 4)
    - Personal, social (correspondents include Eileen Coghlan, Vivian Cowan, Mabel Holdaway, Hilda Richeson, Harriet Laurie Ruiter [Lena's sister], Ruth Schlenske, unidentified), 1924-1938 (Box-folder 59 / 5-15)
  - Financial Records
    - Bank statements and cancelled checks, 1922-1931 (Box-folder 59 / 16-22)
    - Bank statements and cancelled checks: C.R. Cattle and Sheep Company (Wellington D. Rankin), 1929-1930 (Box-folder 60 / 1)
    - Bank statements and cancelled checks: Cook Candy Company, 1927 (Box-folder 60 / 2)
    - Bank statements and cancelled checks: Trustee Account, 1931 (Box-folder 60 / 3)
    - Bills, receipts, etc., 1932-1950 (Box-folder 60 / 4)
    - Commodity and stock accounts, 1923-1955 (Box-folder 60 / 5-7)
    - Stock ownership ledgers and margin trading, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 60 / 8)
    - Miscellaneous (includes livestock shipment memo book; expenses, Gosnell lease account), 1930-1936, n.d. (Box-folder 60 / 9)
  - Legal Documents
    - Apartment lease, New York City, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 60 / 10)
  - Reports
    - Monthly report of water distribution to Hervey Cook on Confederate Creek [scattered], 1929-1935 (Box-folder 60 / 11)
    - "Report of the distilling industry," by Hervey Cook, 1936? (Box-folder 60 / 12)
    - Report on Gould Mine, 1928? (Box-folder 60 / 13)
    - Report to stockholders of Diamond City Mines Company, 1935 (Box-folder 60 / 14)
  - School Notes and Records
    - Irving School, 1911 (Box-folder 60 / 15)
    - St. Paul's School (includes report cards, finances, publications, yearbook, etc.), 1915-1919 (Box-folder 60 / 16-17)
    - Princeton University (includes book store account, financial statement), 1919-1921 (Box-folder 60 / 18)
  - Miscellany
    - Sons of the Revolution membership card; Willow Creek Ranch ad (George B. Sim); toasts; etc.), 1920-1936 (Box-folder 60 / 19)
- Gloria Braid Cook
  - Miscellany
    - Correspondence, bills, court receipt, clippings, etc., 1928-1933, n.d. (Box-folder 61 / 1)
- Lena Gosnell Bowyer Finley Cook
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Robert M. Clarke and others (re legal affairs, inheritance, etc.), 1929-1931 (Box-folder 61 / 2-3)
    - Harriet L. Gosnell (sister-in-law), 1931-1933 (Box-folder 61 / 4)
    - Family and friends (many unidentified), 1931-1933 (Box-folder 61 / 5)
  - Financial Records
    - Checkstubs, 1933 (Box-folder 61 / 6)
    - Financial statements, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 61 / 7)
    - Truman B. Gosnell bills (father), 1929 (Box-folder 61 / 8)
  - Subject Files
    - Harry Bowyer's Canadian property, 1924 (Box-folder 61 / 9)
    - Estate materials, 1934 (Box-folder 61 / 10)
  - Miscellany
    - House floor plans and decoarating ideas, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 61 / 11)
    - European travel itinerary, 1928 (Box-folder 61 / 12-13)
    - European travel brochures, etc., 1928 (Box-folder 61 / 14-16)
    - Memorabilia, address book, etc., n.d. (Box-folder 61 / 17)
- Margaret A. Cook
  - Financial Records
    - Insurance on household furnishings, 1900-1903 (Box-folder 62 / 1)
    - Taxes on Missoula property, 1898-1927 (Box-folder 62 / 2)
  - Legal Documents
    - Miscellaneous (includes deed to Helena Cemetery Association lot, deeds to Missoula lots), 1895-1908 (Box-folder 62 / 3)
- Mary Morgan Cook
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous (correspondents include Frank Hervey Cook, A.B. Cook, Episcopal Diocese of Montana, Mayo Clinic, Mary Agnes Cook, unidentified), 1918-1928, n.d. (Box-folder 62 / 4)
    - Condolences on death of A.B. Cook, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 62 / 5-6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - Letter from Fitch H. Medbury to G.P. Kievenaar (re death of Mary Morgan Cook's mother, and family problems), 1928 (Box-folder 62 / 7)
  - Financial Records
    - Bills, receipts, etc., 1914-1929 (Box-folder 62 / 8)
- Mary Agnes Cook
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Harry P. Bennett, 1923-1925, n.d. (Box-folder 62 / 9)
    - Frank J. Kelly, 1923-1925 (Box-folder 62 / 10)
  - Legal Documents
    - Sales contract on automobile, 1927 (Box-folder 62 / 11)
  - School Notes and Records
    - Miscellaneous (includes Emma Willard School, Knox School, Ossining School, Finch School, Blessed Sacrament Convent, Helena Business College), 1913-1926 (Box-folder 62 / 12)
- Transfers To Other Programs
  - Transfers
    - Lists of printed material, maps, photographs, and artifacts transferred to the Library, Photograph Archives, and Museum respectively (Box-folder 62 / 13)